

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Contact

796662377

mic.kuczynski@gmail.com

Date of Birth

18.12.1990

Linkedin

http://linkedin.com/in/mkuczyn/

Github

http://github.com/michalkuczynski

LANGUAGES

Angielski



SOFTWARE SKILLS

Microsoft Office



Google Workspace



__



Git



D - - I. - .



l inux



Michał Kuczyński Curriculum Vitae

PROFILE

I graduated Technical School as a IT Technician, I finished Python/Django bootcamp at ALX Academy and few other courses and webinars. I'm ambitious person, who want to develop myself in programming and acquire knowledge in practice, under the supervision of experts.

I'm a quick learner and I'm fully involved in new topics. In addition to self-study (tasks, projects), I take part in a scrapping application project, in which I develop as a DevOps and support the development of the back-end. I am a quick learner and I am fully involved in new topics. In addition to self-study (tasks, projects), I take part in a scrapping application project, in which I develop as a DevOps and support the development of the back-end.

EDUCATION

10.2010 - 06.2015

Warsaw University of Technology (Dep. of Engineering Production)

Mechanical engineering

09.2006 - 06.2010

Mechatronic Technical School

IT Technician (specialization: networks and operating systems)

EXPERIENCE

06.2022 - 02.2023

Deutsche Bank Polska S.A.

Junior IT Specialist

- supervision and reporting of the compliance of project implementation in accordance with the methodology
- creating periodic reports and summaries
- support for project managers
- support in the processes of starting and closing projects
- automation of reporting processes
- organization and service of project meetings
- control of work in project teams
- supervision of employee training
- supervision over contracts for IT services
- processing internal IT regulations

03.2020 - 05.2022

Veolia Energia Warszawa S.A.

Fleet Administrator

- management of a fleet of 220 cars (receiving, issuing company cars, services, repairs, inspections, insurance)
- maintaining fleet documentation
- creating internal documents (policies, instructions)
- participation in internal projects regarding the car fleet
- supervising the budget of the car fleet
- ongoing analysis and reporting of car costs
- GPS application monitoring and operation
- fuel card management
- participation in internal and external training

ACHIEVEMENTS

Vocational exam: IT technician diploma

B2 exam in English Driving license. B

Certificate of completion of the **Bootcamp**

Python XL Backend/web course at the ALX

Training Center

Certificate of completion of the Codenga

course: Python Developer

Certificate of participation in Asseco Academy webinars:

- AWS
- Azure

SKILLS

Organization of your own work

Teamwork

Effective planning

Ability to lead a team

Work under time pressure

HOBBIES





Football

Cryminal books





Automotive

Gaming



New technologies

04.2019 - 02.2020

General Property sp. z o.o.

Fleet Specialist

- management of a fleet of 270 cars (receiving, issuing company cars, services, repairs, inspections, insurance)
- maintaining fleet documentation
- drawing up contracts and settling private journeys
- optimizing costs related to the fleet and processing contracts with suppliers
- introduction of a fleet policy
- monitoring compliance with the company's fleet policy by users
- fuel card management
- GPS application monitoring and operation
- creating reports and analyzes on the car fleet

09.2018 - 03.2019

Agencja Ochrony "Juwentus" sp. z o.o. sp. k.

Fleet Specialist

- management of a fleet of 200 cars (receiving, issuing company cars, services, repairs, inspections, insurance)
- negotiating contracts for new cars
- maintaining relationships with suppliers
- comprehensive service for employees in the field of company cars
- preparation of analyzes and reports on company fleet management
- fuel card management

10.2017 - 08.2018

Mirent sp. z o.o.

Rent a Car Specialist

- service for individual and business customers
- customer acquisition
- preparation of commercial offers
- creating contracts, protocols for the release and return of vehicles
- issuing rental invoices
- running a reservation system
- supervising the work of drivers (assigning courses, controlling working time, verifying compliance with procedures)
- management of a fleet of 60 cars

09.2016 - 09.2018

Own Business

Subcontractor

- X-Press Couriers sp. z o.o. (09.2016 05.2017)
- InPost S.A. (06.2017 09.2018)

PERSONALITY

Self-development Non-conflict
Engagement Independence
Responsibility Reliability

Professionalism Analytical thinking skills